<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>

    <string id="st_wpn_avt40">
		<text>AVT-40</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_avt40_descr">
		<text>The AVT-40 is a Soviet automatic rifle developed from the SVT-40. It was developed due to a shortage of machine guns, but the increased strain of automatic fire often caused breakages. Production was relatively brief, none were made after the summer of 1943.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple]• %c[ui_gray_2] PU special scope</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_avt40_short">
		<text>AVT-40 (sawn-off)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_avt40_short_descr">
		<text>The AVT-40 is a Soviet automatic rifle developed from the SVT-40. It was developed due to a shortage of machine guns, but the increased strain of automatic fire often caused breakages. Production was relatively brief, none were made after the summer of 1943. This rifle has had its barrel shortened, allowing it to act as a pistol, the gas tube has also been adjusted to maintain automatic operation. The shortened barrel results in greatly decreased accuracy and muzzle velocity.</text>
	</string>

    <string id="st_wpn_mosin_short">
		<text>Mosin-Nagant (sawn-off)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mosin_short_descr">
		<text>A basic version of the Mosin-Nagant with slightly worn interiors. The M1891/30 was produced for standard issue to all Soviet infantry from 1930 to 1945. It was extremely successful in World War II as a sniper rifle when it was equipped with a 4x PE or a 3.5x PU scope. Due to an abundance of these rifles and a relative scarcity of pistols, sawn-off Mosin-Nagants were often used by those who needed a small, concealable weapon. The shortened barrel results in greatly decreased accuracy and muzzle velocity.</text>
	</string>

    <string id="st_wpn_sks_short">
		<text>SKS (sawn-off)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sks_short_descr">
		<text>The SKS is one of the first weapons chambered for the 7.62x39mm round. Replaced in Soviet front-line service by the AK-47 in the early 1950s, it remained in second-line service for decades and is still used as a ceremonial arm today. This rifle has had its barrel shortened, allowing it to act as a pistol, the gas tube has also been adjusted to maintain semi-automatic operation. The shortened barrel results in greatly decreased accuracy and muzzle velocity.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_svt40_short">
		<text>SVT-40 (sawn-off)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_svt40_short_descr">
		<text>The SVT-40 is a surplus semi-automatic rifle chambered in the 7.62x54mmR round. It saw widespread use in the Red Army and Wehrmacht during WWII. This rifle has had its barrel shortened, allowing it to act as a pistol, the gas tube has also been adjusted to maintain semi-automatic operation. The shortened barrel results in greatly decreased accuracy and muzzle velocity.</text>
	</string>

</string_table>