<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>

    <string id="st_wpn_m1carbine_og">
		<text>M1 Carbine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m1carbine_og_descr">
		<text>The M1 Carbine is a lightweight, semi-automatic carbine that was introduced to US military during World War II. It was meant to be a primary weapon of rear echelon troops and those soldiers who did not need or couldn't carry a long and heavy infantry rifle like M1 Garand. It was very well liked in the WWII and after and is widely regarded as a reliable and effective weapon that is very easy to control even for less experienced shooters. Over 6 millions of these weapons were produced, more than any other US WWII weapon. After the war the M1 was used up until Vietnam war by US and even longer by more than 50 other countries. M1 Carbine was sold in big numbers on civilian market in US, leading it to be a popular rifle for gunsmiths to customize and convert to different calibers. While this tendency has slowed due to shrinking rifle stocks and an increase in value of original configuration rifles, many customized rifles still exist.\n
		The M1 Carbine is chambered in .30-06 Springfield round (7.62x63mm), the standard cartridge back then.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]COMPATIBLE MOD KITS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Default: Gunsmith modification kit</text>
	</string>

    <string id="st_wpn_m1carbine_custom">
		<text>M1 Carbine (custom)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m1carbine_custom_descr">
		<text>The M1 Carbine is a lightweight, semi-automatic carbine that was introduced to US military during World War II. It was meant to be a primary weapon of rear echelon troops and those soldiers who did not need or couldn't carry a long and heavy infantry rifle like M1 Garand. It was very well liked in the WWII and after and is widely regarded as a reliable and effective weapon that is very easy to control even for less experienced shooters. Over 6 millions of these weapons were produced, more than any other US WWII weapon. After the war the M1 was used up until Vietnam war by US and even longer by more than 50 other countries. M1 Carbine was sold in big numbers on civilian market in US, leading it to be a popular rifle for gunsmiths to customize and convert to different calibers. While this tendency has slowed due to shrinking rifle stocks and an increase in value of original configuration rifles, many customized rifles still exist.\n
		This particular rifle has been adapted to fire the more powerful .357 magnum round, and is fed using 9 round Desert Eagle magazines. This variant is somewhat more common in the Zone due to the rarity of the .30 carbine cartridge.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]COMPATIBLE MOD KITS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Default: Gunsmith modification kit</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_m1a1_og">
		<text>M1A1 Carbine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m1a1_og_descr">
		<text>The M1A1 Carbine is a paratrooper variant of M1 Carbine, a lightweight, semi-automatic carbine that was introduced to US military during World War II. It was developed specially for paratroopers, as it was very light and folding stock made it easier to airdrop with it. Apart from folding stock, the weapon is exactly the same. M1 Carbine was meant to be a primary weapon of rear echelon troops and those soldiers who did not need or couldn't carry a long and heavy infantry rifle like M1 Garand. It was very well liked in the WWII and after and is widely regarded as a reliable and effective weapon that is very easy to control even for less experienced shooters. Over 6 millions of these weapons were produced, more than any other US WWII weapon. Unlike the M1 Carbine, the M1A1 is a rare weapon and it is rarely seen outside museums and private collections, however, many fakes and reproductions exist.\n
		This is a "traditional model", so it is chambered in .30-06 Springfield round (7.62x63mm), the standard cartridge back then.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]COMPATIBLE MOD KITS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Default: Gunsmith modification kit</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_m1a1_custom">
		<text>M1A1 Carbine (custom)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m1a1_custom_descr">
		<text>The M1A1 Carbine is a paratrooper variant of M1 Carbine, a lightweight, semi-automatic carbine that was introduced to US military during World War II. It was developed specially for paratroopers, as it was very light and folding stock made it easier to airdrop with it. Apart from folding stock, the weapon is exactly the same. M1 Carbine was meant to be a primary weapon of rear echelon troops and those soldiers who did not need or couldn't carry a long and heavy infantry rifle like M1 Garand. It was very well liked in the WWII and after and is widely regarded as a reliable and effective weapon that is very easy to control even for less experienced shooters. Over 6 millions of these weapons were produced, more than any other US WWII weapon. Unlike the M1 Carbine, the M1A1 is a rare weapon and it is rarely seen outside museums and private collections, however, many fakes and reproductions exist.\n
		Among the more numerous conversions of the M1 Carbine is the 5.7x33mm Johnson cartridge. Parts from rifles of this configuration have been further used to adapt guns to the FN 5.7x28mm cartridge more commonly seen in the Zone, serving as a low cost alternative to the P90.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]COMPATIBLE MOD KITS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Default: Gunsmith modification kit</text>
	</string>

</string_table>