<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>

	<string id="st_wpn_psg1">
		<text>HK SR9 TC</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_psg1_descr">
		<text>The Heckler and Koch SR9 is a series of hunting and target rifles derived from the Heckler &amp; Koch HK91 incorporating parts from the PSG-1 and MSG-90 marksman rifles. In its original configuration it had a thumbhole buttstock, but the SR9 TC (Target Competition) variant replaces this with a PSG-1 adjustable butstock, also including the PSG-1 sniper trigger group and handgrip. As only limited numbers of SR9 TC rifles were produced, it is likely this is a reproduction, created with aftermarket parts and made to better mimic the appearance of the original PSG-1. This rifle's accuracy is not to the level of a true PSG-1, however it is significantly lighter and more durable, allowing it to better function as a DMR.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Hensoldt ZF PSG-1 6x42 scope (integrated)</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_psg1a1">
		<text>HK PSG-1A1</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_psg1a1_descr">
		<text>The PSG-1 is a precision rifle based on the G3 battle rifle. It was designed from the beginning as a police sniper rifle for maximum precision. It boasts very high accuracy, but is also extremely expensive, leading to limited sales and a cessation of production in 2010. After the 1972 Munich massacre, Germany needed a semi-automatic rifle that would provide highest precision possible, eventually resulting in this gun and the WA2000. Mechanically it is just like the G3, though with features lending to higher precision. The PSG-1's accuracy is close to that of bolt-action sniper rifles, which is exceptional for a semi-automatic weapon. The rifle's weight, price and rather delicate construction makes it unsuitable for military use, leading to the development of the MSG90, with improvements aimed towards military conditions. The PSG-1A1 variant features 2 main improvements, an adjustment to the charging handle's position to prevent interference with optics, and an update to a Schmidt &amp; Bender 3–12?50 Police Marksman II scope. \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Schmidt &amp; Bender 3-12x50 scope (integrated)</text>
	</string>

</string_table>