<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>

	<string id="st_wpn_scar_l_descr">
		<text>The Special Operations Forces Combat Assault Rifle (SCAR) is a modular rifle made by FN Herstal for SOCOM to satisfy the requirements of the SCAR competition. This family of rifle consist of two types, the SCAR-H and SCAR-L. The SCAR-L (Light) is chambered in 5.56x45mm NATO cartridge.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45 compatible suppressor\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, C-more Railway Tactical, EOTech scopes\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]COMPATIBLE MOD KITS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Default: Custom modification kit</text>
	</string>

<!-- BaS guns -->
	<string id="st_wpn_pm_bas_descr">
		<text>This Soviet legacy is the most common pistol in the Zone and is one of the best compact self-defence handguns available. It is small, highly reliable, easy to use and maintain in working order. It also suffers from several drawbacks, including short range, low firing accuracy and poor stopping power, while also losing out to modern pistols in its class in terms of weight and magazine size. In 1951, the Pistol Makarova was selected because of its simplicity, easy manufacturing, accuracy, and reasonable stopping power.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]COMPATIBLE MOD KITS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Default: Custom, Specialized modification kits</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_svd_m1_descr">
		<text>Originally intended for designated marksmen in every basic Soviet infantry unit, the Dragunov SVD was not designed for specialised sniper teams. Relatively light for a sniper rifle but well-balanced and having semiautomatic fire, its precision is good but not exceptional. It has an effective range of up to 800 metres.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: All dovetail mount scopes except of except of red dot sights.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: KZRZP suppressor (after modification)\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]COMPATIBLE MOD KITS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Default: Specialized, Mercenary modification kits</text>
	</string>

</string_table>